And I know I can’t seem to find hope
I’ve been trying my hardest to cope
But I get stuck in my head
Think I’m better off dead
And I don’t think that I’ll let them know
Don’t say you love me
You don’t
You just want me to fit in
Your mold
And can we please pretend
That you’ll hold up your end
Or do you really want me to choke?
Don’t say you love me
Don’t say you love me now
And I hope I break down into dust
I still feel my bones turning to rust
But I always pretend
That this pain has an end
But it doesn’t it’s how I wake up
Don’t say you love me
You don’t
You just want me to fit in
Your mold
And can we please pretend
That you’ll hold up your end
Or do you really want me to choke?
Don’t say you love me
Don’t say you love me now